

Personal details



Thomas Raveneau



thomas.raveneau1@gmail.com



+33 6 46 69 73 80



Suresnes, Ile-de-France



March 31st, 2000



Permis B



thomas-raveneau.com



linkedin.com/in/Thomas-Raveneau



github.com/Thomas-Raveneau

Skills

Unreal

Unity

Godot

C++

C#

Visual Studio

Languages

French



English



Hobbies

- Video games
- Cinema
- Tennis

Thomas Raveneau

Gameplay programmer

Profile

French developer student since 4 years and before that amateur in this domain, I developed a strong passion for video games since my childhood.

In highschool, I discovered game development by creating a Monopoly game with Python.

Today my skills in video game development have highly evolved thanks to the projects I did with and in parralel of my studies using my passive learning of 10th art acquired since I was young, today pushing me to develop quality games where the players joy is my biggest concern.

Looking for end-of-studies internships from September 2022 to February 2023 and from March 2023 to August 2023.

Employment

Sharepoint developper

Oct 2020 - Jul 2021

Cegedim, Boulogne-Billancourt

- Development of internal administration tools in C# (data analysis, monitoring, web tracking)
- · Generation of personalized data analysis reports by filtering
- Understand the communicative vision of Cegedim imagined by the director of web communication

Full Stack developper

Jul 2019 - Dec 2019

Onepoint, Paris

- Development of the main communication tool for employees
- · Database development and management
- Processing of user data

Education

Game development

2021 - 2022

Keimyung University, Daegu - South Korea

Done in a university exchange context, I specialized myself for 1 year in video games development by enriching my technical and design skills, studying the following topics:

- Computer graphics (3D transformations, projections, interpolation)
- · Game design
- 3D modeling and animation

Information Technology expert

2018 - 2023

EPITECH, Paris - France

Computer development school focusing its education on project-based teaching, offering students great autonomy.

- Software architecture, object oriented programming
- Multithreading, inter-process communication
- Network programming, serialization

Projects (Github)

Quake (remake)

Video game

FPS multiplayer game developed with Unreal Engine and C++, using a dedicated server. The player is facing another player where the goal is to eliminate his opponent in a limited time using different weapons.

Social Dungeons

Video game

2D game developed with Godot, which put the player in an hostile environment where the goal is to go through multiple rooms, facing enemy waves to eliminate using different spells.

Scratchy

Graphics library (C++)

Developed in C++ using OpenGL (GLFW), this library allow the user to display textured cubes while offering a complete abstraction and a really simple use.